Van den Haag, Ernest; Papers apap135
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Conferences and Meetings, 1947-1999; 7; 0.33 cubic ft.
  - Memorial Conference, "The Legacy of Henry G. Manne", Williamsburg, VA, 1999 May 21-1999 May 22 (Box 1 (7-Conferences and Meetings), Folder 8)
  - Mont Pelerin Society, "Enemies of Freedom: The Capitalists", Address Delivered, ca. 1984-1985 (Box 1 (7-Conferences and Meetings), Folder 9)
  - National Conference on Punishment of Criminal Offences, "The Justification of Punishment", Address Delivered, Ann Arbor, MI, 1987 November 09-1987 November 10 (Box 1 (7-Conferences and Meetings), Folder 10)
  - Social Philosophy and Policy Center, "Crime, Culpability, and Remedy", San Diego, CA, 1989 April 20-1989 April 23 (Box 1 (7-Conferences and Meetings), Folder 11)
  - University at Albany, "The Idea of Criminal Justice", Albany, NY, 1989 April 13-1989 April 14 (Box 1 (7-Conferences and Meetings), Folder 12)
  - University at Albany, "The Death Penalty: Perspectives on the Past and Future in New York State", Albany, NY, 1991 April 14-1991 April 16 (Box 1 (7-Conferences and Meetings), Folder 13)
  - University of Tulsa, "Why Is There So Much Crime?" Address Delivered, Tulsa, OK, 1991 April 11 (Box 1 (7-Conferences and Meetings), Folder 14)